站住别动
That's far enough.
放下衣物袋 慢慢转过身来
Drop your laundry and turn slowly.
这么说你要抢劫?
So you gonna rob me now?
要我提醒你我是谁吗?
I need to remind you who I am?
Omar 对吗?
Omar, isn't it?
把枪慢慢拔出来 扔掉它
Pull it slowly. Then toss it.
我会慢慢拔出来
Oh, I will move slow.
但我不会扔 小礼服
I ain't tossing nothing, Bow Tie.
不管你想干什么  赶紧行动 废话少说
So whatever you gonna do, you might as well go ahead and make it quick.
我知道你会回来
I knew you'd come back.
我想你不会因此失眠吧
I trust you didn't lose sleep over it.
担心你简直是杞人忧天
Worrying about you would be like wondering if the sun gonna come up.
我连眉头都不会皱一下
I ain't about to wild out over it.
但我好奇你怎么找到我的
What I want to know is how you found me.
你的人说的 可吃了不少苦头
Your boy, he didn't give you up easy.
不会是给他注射糖水吧
Ain't no sugar-water run through them veins.
- 你杀了他? - 他死得很安详
- You kill him? - He's resting.
看来你喜欢点45口径
I see you favor a .45.
就今晚
Tonight I do.
顺便告诉你 我家里还留着一把
And I keeps one in the chamber, in case you pondering.
你那把家伙不错
Nice showpiece you got there.
Walther PPK  点380口径 双发
Walther PPK .380, double action.
听说Walther常会打偏
Hear them Walthers like to jump some.
你那把可能会打到你手肘
As will you, with one in your elbow.
我带的子弹还打不残我的关节
That gun ain't got enough firepower to make my joint useless.
但我绝对会不惜火力对付你
It definitely won't stop me from emptying out half my mag.
你可能打不到我
You might not hit me.
在这个射程? 用这种口径?
This range? And this caliber?
即使打偏也能打中你
Even if I miss, I can't miss.
我欣赏自信的人
I admire a man with confidence.
我也没见你流一滴汗 老兄
I don't see no sweat on your brow neither, bro.
也许我们可以在这里站一晚上
I suppose we could stand here all night.
也许吧
Suppose we could.
或者一劳永逸
Or settle this once and forever.
我要问你一件事 老弟
I want to ask you something, brother.
Omar听着呢
Omar listening.
火线重案组 第三季 第11集
the.wire.s03e11
* When you walk through the garden *
* you gotta watch your back *
* well I beg your pardon *
* walk the straight and narrow track *
* if you walk with Jesus *
* he's gonna save your soul *
* you gotta keep the devil *
* way down in the hole *
* he's got the fire and the fury *
* at his command *
* well you don't have to worry *
* if you hold on to Jesus hand *
* we'll all be safe from Satan *
* when the thunder rolls *
* just gotta help me keep the devil *
* way down in the hole *
* you gotta help me keep the devil *
"我们已没有梦想 兄弟" ——Stringer Bell
Sean McGinty 别名"Shamrock" BPI#1214-5
- 我要去西区了 - 好的
- I'm going to the West. - All right.
- 回见 - 好
- Peace out. - All right.
开始了
Here we go.
喂 我要见老板
Yo. I need some face time with the man.
等我打给你
Hold on, I'll holler back at you, man.
那是Shamrock
That'd be Shamrock.
假设Stringer Bell就是老板 我们就坐等回电吧
Assuming Stringer Bell is the man, now we wait for the return call.
干得漂亮
This is beautiful.
Lester 你相信我们把窃听器 卖给了窃听目标吗?
Lester, can you actually believe we fucking sold the wiretaps to the targets.
至少能信一周
For a week at least.
我们可以隐瞒一发子弹
Maybe we ducked a bullet.
悄悄收拾这个烂摊子
Maybe we clean this mess quietly...
对记者随便胡扯一番
throw some horseshit at whatever reporter shows up...
市长就会得饶人处且饶人
and the Mayor forgives and forgets.
我们已准备好行动了吧?
We're ready to move on this, right?
只要上头一发令  我们就封锁整三个区
As soon as we get the word, we shut down all three zones...
让所有人全部上车
toss everyone into wagons.
午夜换班前不会留下蛛丝马迹
There'll be nothing left of it before midnight shift.
那还要等一天半干什么?
So what the fuck are we waiting on for a day and half?
市政厅为何不召集我们?
Why isn't the Hall calling us?
- 市长办公室 - Burrel局长要找Royce市长
- Mayor's Office. - Commissioner Burrell for Mayor Royce.
- 够了 - 别急 Coleman
- I've heard enough. - Hold on, Coleman.
拜托 听他说完
Come on, let the man talk, huh?
打扰了 市长 Burrell局长来电
Excuse me, Mayor. I have Commissioner Burrell on the line.
- 他说有要事 - 没错
- He says it's urgent. - I'll bet it is.
他想要行动了 Clarence
He wants to move, Clarence.
他想收拾昨天的烂摊子 我们也想
He wants to clean this shit up yesterday, and so do we.
让他等等 你继续说 Gene
Tell him to hold. Go ahead, Gene.
听着 我不懂政治 我只是个学者
Look, I'm not a politician, I'm an academic.
我只知道从公众健康的角度看
All I know is that from a public health perspective...
自由贸易区里正发生非同寻常的事
there are remarkable things happening in the free zones.
毒品交易 现场验血 发放安全套
Needle exchanges, on-site blood testing, condom distribution.
最难的是这帮人大多很特殊
Most of all, we're interacting with an at-risk community that is largely elusive.
我们甚至要说服一些人 接受戒毒
I mean, we're even talking some of these people into drug treatment.
这就是UM和Bon Secours 在谈的事情
And that's just what UM and Bon Secours have brought to the table.
如果它被批准
If this thing were sanctioned...
我的部门可以调动公共资源
my department could put public resources into play.
你们没有看清大局
You people can't see the forest here.
Odell?
这事万一泄露出去 部长们肯定会反对你
When the story breaks, the ministers will surely be against you.
市政厅大部分人员都会倒戈
And most of the City Council will be walking sideways...
离开你的部门
away from your administration.
我猜想州长和立法机构
And my guess is the Governor and the Legislature...
会利用这次机会把事情闹大
will use this opportunity to piss on the city from a great height.
而华盛顿呢?
And Washington?
你能想象美国司法部有多想
Can you imagine how far the United States Department of Justice...
在背后戳你脊梁骨吗?
is gonna crawl up your ass behind this?
犯罪率下降了 Odell
Crime is down, Odell.
医疗部门告诉我这办法可行
Medical people are telling me this could work.
全城重罪率已下降14%
I mean, a 14% decline in felonies citywide...
他们可能查不到我 我们得好好想想
I might be untouchable on this. Now, look, we need to think.
能否在掩盖事实的基础上继续执行
See if we can keep this thing going without calling it what it really is, huh?
- 老天 - 肯定会有办法的
- Jesus. - Now, there's got to be a way.
我要你们详细讨论一下 喂 Erv 久等
I want you to talk this thing out. Hey, Erv, thanks for holding.
没错 但...
Yes, but...
是 我理解
Yes, I understand.
那我等你消息
Then I'll wait to hear from you.
Hamsterdam的任何行动必须延后
We're to hold off on any action in Hamsterdam.
在接到通知前不许行动 不准捉拿任何人
No arrests, no movement until further notice.
他说他要重组
He says he wants to regroup.
确定最有效的行动方针
Determine the most effective course of action.
给我解释一遍 Erv
Translate that for me, will you, Erv?
我可听不懂他的鸟语
I don't speak his fucked-up lingo.
Royce正想办法 把我们所有人送上断头台
Royce is figuring a way to put all of us in the guillotine...
而不让市政厅发生任何流血事件
and keep the blood from spraying anywhere near the Hall.
见鬼 要是我这样退出就死定了
Shit, I'll be goddamned if I'm gonna go out like that.
转向公众
Bent over in public.
我可以和那混蛋一样编故事
I can spin the story just as well as that motherfucker.
你要告诉媒体?
You're gonna go to the press?
我不会
Not me.
但我认识一个不在乎恶名的小滑头
But I know a slick little bastard who will happily put His Honor's shit in the street.
发现问题了吗?
Something funny about that?
我只看到文件里有政府拨款  但B&B一个子儿也没有
'Cause I look in the paper and I see all these Federal grants coming down, but nothing for B&B.
你想有什么?
You're expecting what?
还款 付清我们预支的一大笔钱
Payout. A big payout for what we put in, man.
政府给戒毒所拨的款
Federal dollars on them Howard Street rehabs.
- 你预支了钱? - 是的 25万美金
- You gave money up front? - $250,000, yep.
付给Clay Davis?
To Clay Davis.
你怎么知道?
How you know?
你想说什么? 他在耍我?
What you saying? He's running game?
不会的 他还没这么无耻
No, hell, no, he ain't that brazen.
让我猜猜
Let me guess.
他跟你说了水龙头
He's told you about the faucet.
还是下金蛋的鹅?
Or was it the goose that laid the golden egg?
你见过真人吗?
You ever actually meet the man?
你亲眼见到你的钱 交到政府人员手里吗?
Did you ever actually see any of your cash reach anyone in authority?
是的 我见过联邦大楼里的人  我见过他
Yeah, I met the guy at the Federal Building. Yeah, I met him.
是吗? 哪间办公室?
Yeah? What office?
他下楼到大厅来的
He came down to the lobby.
他给你设了圈套
He rainmade you.
一个人说如果你付钱给他 他能求到雨
A guy says if you pay him, he can make it rain.
你给他钱  如果真下雨 就是他的功劳
You pay him. If and when it rains, he takes the credit.
如果没有下  他就让你付更多的钱给他
If and when it doesn't, he finds reasons for you to pay him more.
Clay Davis耍了你
Clay Davis rainmade you.
不可能...他一转眼就 得到了进出大楼的许可
No, man... he got them building permits in no time at all, man.
我们贿赂了这帮混蛋
I mean, we bribing these motherfuckers.
- 他追回了市政建设的承包费 - 多少?
- He got the city contractor's money back. - How much?
- 至今有3万5美金 - 而你给了他25万?
- $35,000 so far. - On the $250,000 you gave him?
- 这是贿赂的钱 - 根本就没有贿赂!
- It's for bribing the motherfuckers. - There are no bribes!
你真以为一位州参议员 愿意拿薪水
You really think a State Senator is going to risk his salary...
和职位冒险 带着装满毒品赃款的手提箱
and his position by walking into a Federal office...
大摇大摆走进联邦大楼?
with a briefcase full of drug money?
我还见到Chunky  Chunky Coates
I seen Chunky, Chunky Coates.
Chunky Coates和大家一样领拨款
Chunky Coates gets his grant money same way everyone does.
他填写申请 确保计划符合规格
He fills out applications, he makes sure the plans meet spec...
然后拼命祈祷
then he prays like hell.
这是城里的老把戏了  而Clay Davis?
This is an old game in this town, and Clay Davis?
他天生就是个贼
That ganef was born with his hand in someone's pocket.
我只希望你能早点来找我
I just wish you'd run it by me sooner.
现在Shamrock在回Bodie的电话
Now here's Shamrock returning Bodie's call.
快说
Talk light.
老板说和你老时间见
Yo, the man said he'd see you same time as always.
- 你知道地点 - 在第一次通话中
- You know the spot. - During the first call...
Sydnor在西巴尔的摩 安排了眼线跟踪Shamrock 对吧?
Sydnor had eyes on Shamrock over in West Baltimore. All right?
现在看这里
Now look at this.
那时Stringer Bell在打印店门口
At the time, Stringer Bell was at the print shop.
所以他们不可能碰面
So it couldn't be a face-to-face meet.
我们没有收到Stringer和 Shamrock之间的通话
We didn't catch a call between Stringer and Shamrock.
怎么会呢?
How can that be?
Stringer和他手下的电话 不在同一个服务区
Stringer's phone isn't on the same network as everyone below him.
说得没错 女士
Right you are, ma'am.
Bell没有用Bernard的手机
Bell's not using Bernard's burners.
而Shamrock用另一部手机打给了Bell
And Shamrock has a separate phone for calling Bell.
我们听不到那些通话 因为系统被分隔了
We can't hear those calls because the system's compartmentalized.
这帮混蛋真够狡猾的
They're some tricky motherfuckers.
监听Bernard的电话一周左右 我们就能查出每个人
A week or so up on Bernard's phones and we'll have everybody...
还能查到Shamrock涉嫌共谋罪
up to and including Shamrock, tangled up in conspiracy counts.
但Bell或Barksdale?
But Bell or Barksdale?
除非能接收到他们的手机信号
Not unless we can pluck their cell numbers out of the air.
- 你要上哪儿去? - 玩具店
- Where you headed? - Toy store.
他在特区将毒品合法化?
He legalized drugs in special zones?
不仅如此
It's more than that.
Colvin局长已经失去了领导
Major Colvin lost the necessary perspective...
所必须具备的判断力
that is required for command.
现在我们都受到 犯罪率年终考核的压力
Now, we were all under pressure to reduce crime before year-end...
他却丝毫不为所动
and he responded poorly to that pressure.
谁给的压力? 市长?
Pressure by who? Mayor?
我只是在跟你解释
I'm just explaining to you...
压力是自上而下的
that the pressure was applied all down the line...
从总部到地方指挥官
from Headquarters to the District Commanders...
到轮班和部门监管
to the shift and sector supervisors.
原来Colvin的14%降幅是胡扯
So Colvin's 14% decline was bullshit.
他们还经警方允许在西区贩毒?
And they're selling drugs with police permission in Western?
政府
The Department
准备开展大规模肃清行动
is ready to shut that mess down with mass arrests.
我是负责人
I'm on top of it.
你为什么还不行动?
Why don't you move?
市长要我们等
The Mayor says wait.
为什么?
Why?
我认为他要演一场戏
I think he's gonna make some kind of show.
让我来承担与我毫无关联的责任
Spin it so that I take the weight for something that has nothing to do with me,
这样我的上级会直接
and everything to do with the pressure that my Commanders
受到市政厅的影响
were getting from City Hall.
推诚布公 把责任推还给市政厅
Going public and putting the responsibility for this
是我唯一的出路了 懂吗?
back at City Hall is the only move I have left, right?
我必须先下手为强
I mean, I spin Royce before he spins me.
- 那你要我... - 不 不是你
- And you want me to... - No, no, not you.
你的朋友 Tony Gray
Your pal, Tony Gray.
如果他要对付Royce 他需要弹药吧?
If he's gonna take a run at Royce, he's gonna need ammunition, right?
我和Gray不熟 但和你熟
I don't have a relationship with Gray. I do have one with you.
议员 你欠我的
And, Councilman, you owe me.
- 有事吗 帅哥? - 我有个技术性问题
- What's up, hotshot? - I got a technical question.
记得我们以前接收电话信号的 模拟装置吗?
Remember those analog units we used to use to pull cell numbers out of the air?
CF什么的
CF-something-something.
是的 CFID(电信频率识别装置)  "炮弹鱼"
Yeah, cell frequency identification device. The Triggerfish, yeah.
- 没错 它能追踪号码 - 对
- That one. It could flag a number. - Right.
老式模拟器必须紧跟目标
With the old analog machines, we used to have to follow the guy around...
随时在通话时监听  但新装置...
stay close while he used the phone. New digitals?
叮 通过电信塔就能找到号码
Bing, you just pull the number right off the cell tower.
你Woodlawn那里有我能借用的吗?
So, you got any down out at Woodlawn that Daddy can borrow?
- 你的呢? - 什么?
- What about yours? - What?
市内有三台 我没记错吧
City has three of them, I remember right.
国土安全局授权给你们的 每个州级政府部门都有
Homeland Security grant sent them to you, every big county department in the state.
他妈不可能吧
No fucking way.
谢谢
Thanks.
- 我很怀疑 Tommy - 我告诉过你事关重大
- I doubted you, Tommy. - I told you it was big.
如果我们处理得当
If we play it right.
他要我把消息透露给Tony Gray
He wants me to turn the information over to Tony Gray let him use it.
他说如果Tony跟市长对着干
He figures if Tony's gonna be running against the Mayor...
他会对准Royce 而不是政府
he'll take aim at Royce and not the Department.
你可以把Tony扯进来 让他继续牵制市长
You may want to bring Tony in on it, keep him viable against the Mayor.
但现在你要查出到底怎么回事
But right now, you need to find out what this is all about.
首先 你认识Colvin局长吗?
Firsthand. Do you know this Major Colvin?
可能打过照面
To shake hands, maybe.
如果Burrell当他是恶人
If Burrell's painting him the villain...
Colvin可能等不及要说他的看法
Colvin might be anxious to tell someone his side of the story.
McNulty 重案组
McNulty, Major Crimes.
Sullivan 轻微恼人组
Sullivan, minor irritations.
你里面有像CFID 却是数字信号的装置吗?
You got anything back there that's like the old CFID, but digital?
- 追踪手机号用的? - 追踪谁?
- For catching cell numbers? - Catching who?
你知道 "炮弹鱼"
You know, a Triggerfish machine.
追踪手机号的"炮弹鱼"
Triggerfish. For cell numbers.
我自己进去看行吗?
How about I look around there on my own?
对 我是市政厅的Carcetti议员
Yes, this is Councilman Carcetti over at the Hall.
- 我想找Colvin局长 - 对不起 他在度假
- I'm trying to reach Major Colvin. - I'm sorry, but he's on vacation.
我知道 我有公事找他
I'm aware of that but I'm trying to reach him on municipal business.
我可以帮你接通语音信箱
Well, I can put you through to his voicemail.
不要语音信箱 我说要马上联系他
No, not his voicemail. I said I have to reach him immediately.
- 马上? - 对
- Immediately? - Right.
- 他的手机号可以吗? - 手机? 可以
- How about his cell phone? - His cell? Yeah, that would be fine.
行了
All right.
行了 到此为止
All right, that's enough.
没错 我知道手会疼
Yeah, I know, it hurts.
但练一段时间后 你的拳头就会坚如磐石
But your fists gonna be like rocks after awhile.
Justin 过来
Justin, come here.
好 我要你打我胸口
All right. I want you to push me in my chest.
不必太用力
You ain't got to do it hard.
你就是这样站位的
That's how you were standing.
你的后脚没有站稳
You ain't had no weight on your back foot.
对了 没有找准重心
That's right. No center of gravity.
而且如果你站得对
Plus, if you get your stance right...
你就能让你的出拳从腰部发力
then you got the means to put your hip into the punch.
对吧?
Right?
这才是你力量的来源
That's where your power'll come from.
- 是啊 但如果我们被打呢? - 你说什么?
- Yeah, but what happen when we get hit? - Say what?
我们被打呢 即使戴着头套
We get hit, even with this pad...
你就被吓退了
you gonna get trucked.
这身装备就完全没用
All this stuff falling apart.
对 还有沙袋
Yeah, the heavy bag, too.
这些你从哪里弄来的? 原始世界?
Yeah, where you get this stuff at? The town of Bedrock?
不 他说没人 所以你得在这里等
No, he say, "Nobody." So you gonna have to wait right here.
"在这里等"是什么意思? 知道我是谁吗?
What you mean, "Wait right here?" You know who I am, boy?
这个人说想见Avon
Man say he want to see Avon.
让我等着见我自己的搭档
Making me wait to see my own partner.
- 他是新来的 String - 去他的
- He new, String. - Fuck that.
这里有很多新面孔 要我说太多了
Lot of new faces round here, man. Way too many, you ask me.
给我滚出去
Get the fuck out of here.
Avon在哪里?
Where Avon at?
他马上过来
He'll be along shortly.
很好 因为我是来见你的
That's good, 'cause I came to see you, anyway.
你要什么?
What you need?
我要你去杀一个人
I need you to hit somebody.
杀谁?
Who we hitting?
Clay Davis
Clay Davis.
传说中的Clay Davis?
The Clay Davis?
当官的Clay Davis?
Downtown Clay Davis?
你想说明什么吗?
Is that suppose to mean something to me, man?
- 那家伙需要教训 - 见鬼 String 谋杀算不了什么
- That nigga need to be got. - Shit, String, murder ain't no thing.
但这可是暗杀行动...
But this here is some assassination shit...
叫你杀就杀 我不是在求你
I tell you you getting somebody, you getting him. I ain't asking.
- 该死的 String 我不知道... - 黑鬼
- Damn, String, I don't know... - Nigga,
要我提醒你为谁干活吗?
I got to remind you who the fuck you work for?
喂
Hey, yo.
我觉得Slim真不该插手 老大
I think Slim gonna have to sit this one out, boss.
你现在要去杀州参议员了?
So you finna go hit a State Senator now, huh?
你杀了他那样的大人物...
Yo, you kill a downtown nigga like that...
整个世界都会驻足观望
the whole world gonna stand up and take notice.
我说的可是州警 政府官员
I'm talking about the State Police, Federals,
所有这些人
all of that.
你得找个职业杀手来干些这样的事
You need a Day of the Jackal type motherfucker, basically to do some shit like that...
而不是Slim这样的毛头小子
not a rough-and-tumble nigga like Slim.
那家伙拿了我们的钱
That nigga took our money, man.
我早料到了
I seen it coming.
他得消失
Well, he got to go.
不 你是他妈的生意人 你得自负全责
No, you a fucking businessman. You wanna handle it like that.
你不想让所有帮派 闹得天下大乱吧?
You don't wanna get all gangster wild with it and shit, right?
我早说过 不按他们的规矩来会吃苦头
What I tell you about playing them fucking away games?
是啊
Yeah.
你这点动静他们老远就能看到 小子
They saw your ghetto ass coming from miles away, nigga.
你想和他们作对?
You got a fucking beef with them?
倒霉的可会是你
That shit is on you.
我们让它对准最近的电信塔
So, we aim this at the nearest cell tower...
我们要找的Bell收发的信号
the one that would be the conduit for calls...
都通过这座塔来中转
coming to and from our boy, Bell...
然后听其自然
and we let rip.
神了
Fucking hell.
看起来像没写名字的 巴尔的摩白皮书
Looks like Baltimore White Pages without any names.
但线迹追踪器会记录下来
But the pattern tracer'll pull that down.
如果我们知道Bell大致的通话时间
You know, if we know the approximate time of Bell's call...
我们可以从记录那时的信号开始
we could start just by pulling calls off that tower at that time.
那可有上千种
That could be thousands.
是啊 那是端线  但我们有二次拨号
Yeah, that's the base line, but we get a second hit...
那样就缩小到几十种
and that list comes down to dozens.
- 三四次后... - 我们就可以追到这个号码
- And after a third or fourth... - Then we've got his number.
我难以相信它就在ISD里积灰尘 (ISD:信息系统部)
I can't believe that this was just sitting over at ISD, gathering dust.
Lester 我们马上就要 找到这帮混蛋了
We're going to be on these motherfuckers for real now, Lester.
他们还不知道这种技术
Well, they don't know about this technology yet.
这次他们不能改变和调整
For once they can't change and adjust.
太有才了
It's genius.
有事吗?
Need something?
你能赚多少?
Yeah, how much you make, man?
什么?
What?
卖这些T恤 你能赚多少?
On them tees? How much you make?
正经生意 赚不了多少
Fair profit. No more than that.
你也许应该卖带帽T恤
You should probably sell sweats with hoodies.
因为快要换季了
Since the season's changing and all.
你住在哪里?
Where you live at?
卖Yellow Top Yellow Top...
Yellow tops, yellow tops, got them yellow tops.
- Bodie Broadus - 拳击运动员
- Bodie Broadus. - The man with the hands.
我听说你要开拳击馆
I heard you was opening up a gym or something.
是啊 想开
Yeah, trying to.
我想联系Avon
I'm looking to get up with Avon.
我以为你已经抽身了
Thought you was out.
嘿 所以我才来找你
Hey, man, that's why I came to you.
想到我们造成的局面
I mean, I feel like the way we left it,
我不能对他坐视不管
I can't just roll up on the man, you know?
喂 是我
Hey, yo, it's me.
那个打手在我这里
Yo, I got that hitter here with me.
那个加入又退出的兵
Yeah, the soldier that walked in and out.
是 他想见老板
Yeah, he want to see the top man.
你打这么多 总有一天会毙命的
You slam shit like that, you gonna fall out one day.
没事
I'm good.
我在教你 孩子 你就是不想学
I'm trying to school you, boy, and you just don't wanna know.
我没事 挺好的
I'm cool. I'm good.
白T大甩卖 白T大甩卖
Whitey sale, whitey sale.
买三送一 买五送三
One for three, three for five.
白T大甩卖 白T大甩卖
Whitey sale, whitey sale.
Whitey sale, whitey sale,
白T大甩卖  买三送一 买五送三
whitey sale, here. One for three, three for five.
买两件
???
白T大甩卖 白T大甩卖
Whitey sale, whitey sale.
Whitey sale, whitey sale!
好 你想让我跟老板说什么?
All right, so what you want me to tell the man?
帮我打声招呼 我再打给你
Yo, I'll give word up, then I'll hit you back.
这是Shamrock
Shamrock.
下午4:40
4:40 p.m.
B&B公司
B&B Enterprises.
我们要吃午饭
We need to have lunch.
好吧 等会儿打给你
All right, hold on. I'll call you back.
喂
Yo.
- 喂 是我 - 有什么消息?
- Hey, it's me. - What's good?
喂 是我
Yeah, it's me.
告诉那个打手 老板会去接他
Yo, tell the hitter, tell him the tall man will pick him up.
- 好 - 4:47
- Right. - 4:47.
有7分钟时间
Seven-minute window.
里面有892个号码  那是我们的端线
There's 892 phone numbers. That's our base line.
- 我们马上就要成功了 - 没错
- We're on our way. - Yep.
政府拨款申请
他妈的待着别动
Stay the fuck there, man.
喂
Yo.
Jimmy! 在用公开手机号
Jimmy! On the clean phone.
他刚拨了你朋友的号码
He just hit your friend's number.
你给我的名片上有这号
The one off the business card you gave me.
西区?
The Western?
他的手机
His cell.
我们会有麻烦吗?
Should we be worried about this?
不会
No.
拳击馆?
A boxing gym, huh?
还不够完善 所以我要见你
Ain't a proper one yet. That's why I asked to see you.
那你对这类行当有什么打算?
So, what you know about taking care of something like that?
没多少 但我会打拳
Not a damn thing. But I know that sweet science.
还认识几个感兴趣的孩子
And I got some kids who are interested.
但我真正需要的是装备
But what I got a need for, brother, is equipment.
这些孩子常要被猛打
Man, these kids gonna get rained on.
他们需要头盔 护甲 护套
They need headgear, they need guards, cups,
这样才能承受攻击
you know... so they can take the hit.
见鬼 你懂我的意思
Shoot, you know what I'm saying, man.
我在球形海报上见过你的照片
I seen your picture on them Globe posters back in the day.
也许那时缺钱用
Little undercard shit, maybe, you know.
但你还是金手套
Yeah, but still, you was Golden Gloves.
只是一时 后来我受了伤
For a minute, but I had a physical defect.
怎么 你下巴碎了?
What, you got a glass jaw?
不 是额头 朋友
No, forehead, nigga.
打在头盖骨上就出事了
Cranium shot'll do you wrong.
好吧 看这里
yeah. Yo, look here, man.
看到新的练习袋了?
You see the new heavy bags?
看 立式的
Look, freestanding, man.
你只需加水
All you gotta do is add water.
还有速度球 就在这里 看见没?
Then you got speed bags, right there, right?
这里还有新式头盔
You got this headgear right here. It's new.
可以保护脸颊和下巴
Look, protect the cheek and the chin, you know?
我可以四处筹款 这里借点 那里借点
And I know I can go around and collect a dollar here and a dollar there.
但我要组一支精良的团队
But I'm trying to put together a select group of people, right?
我叫它"金环俱乐部"
I call them my Gold Circle Club...
他们能做出巨大的贡献
and they gonna make a substantial contribution...
还能让资金运转起来
and just get this thing rolling right.
我要把他们的名字和照片 贴到拳击馆的墙上
I mean, I'm gonna put their name and picture up on the wall in the gym.
你想让我加入你的俱乐部?
What, you trying to get me to join a club?
不是 我只是想说
No, man, I'm just saying.
里面有各种等级
There's all sorts of levels.
我们有"银环" 还有"铜环"
We got the, the Silver Club, we got the Bronze Club.
针对那些不想深入学习的小子
Man, for motherfuckers who really don't want to dig that deep.
想想吧 老弟 看这里
Come on, man, check it out.
不必了 我没时间听你这些废话
No, man, I ain't got no time for this bullshit, man.
你知道我不想 让自己的名字和脸出现在墙上
And you know I don't want my fucking name and face on no damn wall.
你疯了吗?
You crazy, nigga?
到底要多少钱?
How much money you talking about?
1万美金
$10,000.
就为了1万费这么多口舌?
See him go through all that for $10,000?
Slim 给他取1万5现金
Man, Slim, go get him $15,000 cash, man.
喂...
Yo...
见鬼
Shit.
- 好了 回见 - 好
- All right. Later, man. - yeah.
喂 照顾好那帮小鬼 听到了吗?
Hey, you take care of them little niggas, you hear?
一定会的 兄弟
Yeah, no doubt, bro.
- 喂 - 喂 你跟他谈了吗?
- Yeah. - Yo, you talk to him?
胖子想要连本带利
Fat man wanna parlay.
好吧 保重 即时联系
All right, you good. Hook me up.
好的
Yeah, all right.
看到我给你的东西了?
You check out what I sent you?
是的 你的消息不错
Yeah, your information's good.
现在我们能坦诚相待了吗?
So, we can talk on the real side now, huh?
告诉你的人我明天可以来
Tell your man I'm good for tomorrow.
好 我再打给你
Yo, I'll hit you back.
- 现在成了 - 势如破竹啊
- Now we're cooking. - Cutting butter with a hot knife.
下次Stringer Bell接到端线电话 我们就能瓮中捉鳖
Next time Stringer Bell takes a call off the base line, he's ours.
游戏结束
Game over.
所以不是你想的那么简单的
So, it ain't what it might seem to you.
那个人是我兄弟
That man there is my brother.
但如果一直这样 那么...
But if it keep on like it been, then...
我操
Oh, fuck.
有麻烦吗?
You got problems?
我和Hamsterdam的事有点瓜葛
I stirred up some shit with this Hamsterdam mess.
因为你是幕后主手
That's 'cause you was behind that...
所以我才会找上你
that made me come to you with this.
看来我们俩都在努力弄清这场游戏
Look like you and me both trying to make sense of this game.
这是实话 Russell
Speak your mind, Russell.
我们之间没问题吧?
We two good?
不对
Yeah.
我们先出去了 走吧 P-Square
We got y'all out front. Let's go, P-Square.
你气色不错
You look healthy.
对中过枪的人来说是这样
For a man who was gut-shot.
你找了个中间人
You reached out to a third party...
他雇我来管理你的大楼
who engaged me in the purpose of holding your Towers.
中间人的话就是你的话 他代表你
That third person's word was your word, as he represented you.
没错
That's right.
我除掉了巴尔的摩东区的先生们
And I ran those East Baltimore gentlemen off.
我自始至终遵守了协议
I held up my end of the agreement...
至少在我身体健全时
at least for as long as I was physically able.
没错
You did.
接着你的人在Butchie酒吧 安排了见面
Your man then set up a meet at Butchie's bar.
你的人告诉Omar Little是我
Your man told Omar Little that I was responsible for the torture
折磨了他心爱的男孩儿
of a young boy who was close to Mr. Little's heart.
你的人其实想...
Your man, in effect...
找人杀我
sought to have me hit.
Omar说的你就信了?
Omar told you that and you believe that motherfucker?
我看他不像是会编故事的人
He doesn't strike me as a man who would tell stories.
即使以性命相要挟
Even at the point of dying.
该死
Shit.
"Proposition Joe协议"
Proposition Joe package.
你的组织内部与我无关
The inner workings of your organization don't concern me.
如果有办法...我的人...
If there's a way, I mean, if my man...
如果他犯了错
If he made a mistake here,
我愿意承担责任
then I'm willing to pay the cost.
我们怎么解决?
How can we fix it?
你要钱吗?
You want money?
- 钱? - 是的 这是生意上的事儿
- Money? - Yeah, this is business.
你现在是个生意人没错
Business is where you are now.
但你有今天靠的是信誉和名声
But what got you here is your word and your reputation.
单这一点  你就可以在纽约重新开始
With that alone, you've still got an open line to New York.
如果没有 你就玩完了
Without it, you're done.
我的人还在保释期
My man's still on paper.
我能把他安排到重型武器库
I can put him in a spot that got heavy artillery.
我指的不是小手枪  我说的是TEC-9微冲 散弹枪
I ain't talking about pistols. I'm talking about mini TEC-9s, shotguns,
他们甚至有手榴弹
they even got grenades in that motherfucker.
- 那简直是自寻死路 - 所以希望你能悠着点
That's a automatic fall. So, I'm hoping you could keep that shit to five.
如果你打中了
Look, if you hit the joint...
他的人会努力承担罪责
his people are gonna try and take the rap for it.
他们会承认都是他们开的枪
They gonna say all that firepower is theirs.
你要做的就是 在保释犯的掩护下打中他
So all you gotta do is just hit him with the parole backup.
听着 我保证不了什么
Look, I can't make no promises.
- 但至少会判五年刑 - 拜托 老兄
- It's gonna be a nickel, at least. - Come on, man.
- 他和我... - 我尽力而为 好吗?
- Him and me... - I'm gonna do my best, all right?
他一直待在老巢?
He's always at this place?
不 他会走动
No, he come and go.
但一旦开战 那里就能找到他
But it's the spot since the war started.
他肯定对你做了什么事
He must have done something to you.
不 只是生意而已
No, it's just business.
差点忘了 昨晚有人打给你
Almost forgot. This came in for you last night.
她说打你手机你没接
Said she called your cell phone, but you didn't answer.
声音很甜 像小猫咪
Had a nice voice. Like a kitty cat.
有通话
We're on.
- 他要你过去等 矮子 - 行 好的
- He said for you to be there, half-pint. - Yeah, okay.
- Stringer Bell 就是他 - 找到了
- Stringer Bell, that's him. - There it is.
是啊 但能多久?
Yeah, but for how long?
他随时都可以扔掉手机
He could toss that burner at any moment.
- 我找Rhonda 你联系Daniels - 好
- I got Rhonda, you raise Daniels. - Okay.
- Ronnie? 对 我们在Stringer的线上 - 队长
- Ronnie? Yeah, we're on Stringer's phone. - Lieutenant.
你马上去找法官 我拿到宣誓书后去找你
You should go straight to the judge. I'll meet you there with an affidavit.
- Lester在联系Daniels - McNulty在和Pearlman通话
- Lester's raising Daniels. - McNulty's calling Pearlman.
注意走位 孩子 好的
Watch that footwork, baby. All right.
现在进攻
Take it to him, now.
对 现在进攻
Yeah. Take it to him, now.
没人能打倒我 教练
I'm a beast, coach.
好了 别自吹自擂
All right, boy, don't be gloating on it.
我们什么时候开始实战?
Yo, when we gonna have some real fights?
你知道 去参加比赛
You know, one of them tournament things.
对啊 我们现在是角斗士
Yeah, we gladiators, son.
你们的热情高过实力
Y'all got more fire than skills.
你们还不够格参加职业赛
You ain't ready for no full-blown thing just yet.
不过和不认识的对手训练 也许对你们有好处
But I don't know, maybe it'd be good for y'all to spar with some boys you don't know.
如果有人闯进我家 就会被我摔倒
A nigga step in my house, he getting dropped.
我在宾州大道的拳击馆碰到一帮人
Yo, I met these fellas at that gym over on Pennsylvania Avenue.
我去问问他们想不想参加
I'll see if they wanna roll through, all right?
- 好 - 好
- All right. - All right.
你竟然不回议员的电话?
You don't return a Councilman's calls?
我这周休息
I'm off this week.
休了几天假
Taking a little accrued vacation.
是啊 我听说了原因
Yeah. And I heard why.
我是来听你解释的
I'm here for your side of this story.
如果你不说  Burrell的任何话都是可信的
If I can't get that then whatever comes out of Burrell's mouth is gonna stand.
你可以忍受吗?
You good with that?
你干了什么 局长?
What did you do, Major?
他们为什么没有去扫清?
And why the fuck haven't they shut it down?
我们目睹了实施法律的强硬手段
We've seen that law enforcement's steamroller approach...
- 都会徒劳无获! - 我真觉得...我真觉得
- is just spitting in the wind! - I really think... I really think
你的办法不错 Clarence
that you're onto something here, Clarence.
但如果继续下去  神不知鬼不觉...
But if you keep it up, before you know it...
他们就会把你当成全美最危险分子
they'll be calling you the most dangerous man in America.
我知道我们现在看起来不堪一击
Well, I know it may appear that we're vulnerable here.
但如果我们在城市其他地区 强行毒品法
But if we enforce the drug laws everywhere else in the city aggressively...
他们为什么不能称之为法治管理?
how can they say we're not a law and order administration?
我们只需找出妥协的办法
Now there's got to be a middle ground here that we have yet to find.
肯定有办法完成大业
There's got to be some way to accomplish this...
而不必彻底翻船
without turning everything upside down.
这里曾是我最糟糕的管区
This used to be one of my worst corners.
就是去年夏天警察遭枪击的社区吧?
This is the neighborhood where a cop got shot last summer, right?
叫Dozerman
Dozerman.
现在看起来很安静
Looks quiet now.
我的大部分其他管区也一样
So do most all my corners.
特工
G-man.
找我有事吗?
So, what's up?
把门关上
Shut the door.
10分钟后我们有张请愿书 要让市法官签字
In 10 minutes we're gonna have an affidavit for a city judge to sign.
- 为了窃听Russell Bell的私人号码 - 干得好
- It's for Russell Bell's dirty cell. - It's a good pull.
那是在五天内查到号码的情况下
It is if Bay Wireless doesn't take five days to process it.
你欠我的 Fitz
You owe me, Fitz.
整件港口案是从你这里开始的
That whole port case came down early behind some ugly shit in your house.
我不在乎你怎么做
Now, I don't care how you do it,
但我今天就要得到窃听许可
but I need my wire today.
这些人两个月前在警车里工作
These guys were in radio cars two months ago,
追踪电话 巡逻街道
chasing calls, clearing corners.
我找他们来跟踪重案
I pulled them to do felony follow-up.
多做正经事 少说废话
More police work, less bullshit,
所以我这里的犯罪率能下降
and that's why my crime is down.
这些数据是真实的
The numbers are true.
他做了什么?
What did he do?
教堂盗窃 14宗
Church burglaries, 14 of them.
走吧
Let's go.
女士
Mademoiselle.
应该叫宣誓者还是宣誓人?
Is it affiant or affiant?
我从没...我从没搞清楚过
I've never been... I've never been clear on that.
Jimmy 你查了Bell很长时间吧?
You been hunting this guy Bell for a long time, haven't you, Jimmy?
有阵子了
A while, yeah.
这名字我看着眼熟
Name's familiar to me.
我们几年前办的案子 是不是他...
That thing that we did a few years back, was he the...
是的
Yeah.
木已成舟 Jimmy
What's done is done, Jimmy.
为了你自己好 放手别管了
Now, for your own fucking sake, just let it go.
开始吧
Come on.
作为宣誓者
As the affiant,
你愿意严肃宣誓  证明文件中所包含的信息属实...
do you solemnly swear and attest that the information contained in this document...
这是近期本地犯罪率最显著的下降
That's the most significant drop in crime in this district in recent history.
街上还是有闹事的小孩
We still got some hard-looking boys out on them streets.
警官 你知道他们的迷你摩托吗?
And, Sergeant, you know them little mini-motorcycles?
我晚上想到这个就失眠
They keeping me up at night.
我们会努力解决
We're working on that.
我一辈子都住在这个社区里
Look, I have been living in this part of the city my whole life.
我可以告诉你 我们小时候也不乖
And I can tell you something. We weren't any angels when we were kids.
你说的那些坏小孩
And those hard boys you talking about...
半数帮派都是闹着玩的
half of them, they's just playing gangster.
他们和我们小时候没啥区别
They ain't no different from what we were.
只不过衣服裤子变长了
Shirts and drawers a little longer, is all.
我真正怀念我的社区的是...
The one thing I do miss about my neighborhood...
我说的是我住的社区
I'm talking about the neighborhood I came up in.
瞧 我们认识那些警察
See, we knew the police.
我们认识一个白人警察
See? We had a white police officer.
我们家就在他的巡逻区
Our house was on his beat, on his foot beat.
他会每晚坐在门外跟我妈妈聊天
And he would be sitting out talking to my mother damn near every night...
就坐在门廊上闲扯
I mean, just sitting out on her stoop, just talking.
告诉你  他的名字叫Frazier O'Leary
And I'm telling you, this man, his name was Frazier O'Leary.
- 他还叫得出我外婆的名字 - 好的 女士
- He even knew my grandmother by name. - Yes, ma'am.
我们开始进入细节讨论
Let's move on to the tip-line information...
对不起 宝贝  真抱歉 我还没说完
I'm so sorry, baby. I'm real sorry, but I was not finished.
让我来告诉你
You see, let me tell you something.
我很久没看到警察 跟我面对面交流了
I have not seen that face-to-face policing in a long while.
很久很久了
- In a very long while. - mm-mm.
直到上个礼拜
Until last week.
一个年轻的黑人警察 走到我的门廊
A young officer, black officer, came by my stoop.
我正坐在门口 他给我一张名片
I was sitting out, gave me his card.
他叫Reggie Ballard 这是他名字
His name is Reggie Ballard, is his name, right?
他坐下来跟我说话 我们只是聊天
And he sat, and he talked to me. We just talked.
现在我认得他的名字和脸 他认得我的名字和脸
And, see, now I know his name and face and he knows my name and face.
你瞧? 让我告诉你
You see? And I'm going to tell you something.
治安就应该是这样
That is how it should be.
我儿子要在街上设一个冰激凌摊位
My son wanna open up one of them snowball stands on the street.
我们还需要申请许可证?
Do we nee  a permit for this?
你见过西区居民开这样的会吗?
You ever seen a West Side community meeting like this one?
其实市区有关部门告诉我...
In fact, the folks downtown at Minor Privileges tell me...
城里根本不能在路边设摊位
that stands aren't allowed in the city right-of-way at all.
现在他们说可以在人行道 设冰激凌摊
Now they do say it is possible to have a snowball stand behind the sidewalk.
你到底来干什么 议员?
Why are you really down here, Councilman?
这里又不是你的管区
I mean, this ain't even your district.
我感兴趣
I'm interested.
我掌管公共安全附属委员会
And I have the Public Safety Subcommittee.
看见那幢楼了吗?
You see that building there?
那是老Stryker的楼
It was the old Stryker building.
原来是殡仪馆
It was a funeral parlor.
西区白人进墓地前的最后一站
The last stop before the cemetery for West Side white folk...
原本这里还有些白人
back when there were still some of those around.
就在那个时候
Right about the time
60年代早期开始实行种族隔离
that Jim Crow was breaking up back in the early '60s...
有人问老Stryker  他们说"Stryker...
somebody asked old man Stryker. they say, "Stryker...
"你要改变策略...
"you gonna change your policy...
"开始收黑人了?"
"and start burying black folk?"
Stryker说...
And Stryker said...
"是啊 但有个条件
"Yeah, on one condition.
"我要一次性把他们都收了"
"That I can do them all at once."
真狂
That's sick.
但你知道吗?
But you know something?
我对那个人充满敬意
I had a lot of respect for that man.
因为不像其他人
'Cause, unlike most folks...
我总能清楚他的立场
I always knew where he stood.
我是公事公办
I'm doing my job.
我给你看了美好的一面
Look, I done showed you the good.
现在去看看丑恶的一面
Come on, let me show you the ugly.
嘿
Hey.
怎么那么快?
How come so quick?
Stringer Bell的名字
Stringer Bell's given name.
Russell
Russell.
现在是...
For now?
Ahmed（伊斯兰教的名字)
Ahmed.
我们已到达山顶
We're on the top of the mountain.
Red Top 快来买啊
Red tops over here. Come get them, come get them.????
- 就是这里? - 3个里头的1个
- This is it? - One of three.
你怎么让它成这样?
How did you make this happen?
就成了这样
I just did it.
我听厌了他们说要采取什么措施...
I got tired of hearing folks talk about what needs to be done...
如果他们来做会怎么样等等
or what they would do if it was up to them.
- 瓶装火箭 瓶装火箭 - 这就是你的疑问?
- Bottle rockets, got them bottle rockets. - So, this is about you making a mark?
我没分析那么透彻
No, I ain't analyzed it all that deep.
我也没有欢呼胜利
I ain't claiming no kind of victory, neither.
只能说很高兴自己努力了
I will say I'm glad I tried.
往前走 议员
Go on, Councilman.
我在这里等你
I'll wait for you down here.
你不来吗?
You're not coming?
你看到的景象并不美
What you gonna see ain't pretty.
但很安全
But it's safe.
大杀器 大杀器
WMDs, got them WMDs.
我觉得你应该独自走完这段路
I think you need to take this journey your own self.
Yellow Top 这里有Yellow Top
Got those yellow, those yellow tops. Yellow tops right here.
我给你点了一份
I ordered one for you.
谢谢
Thanks.
- 接到我电话很吃惊? - 有一点
- Surprised I called? - A little.
我们上次分开的情形可不妙
After the way we left it.
我是开朗型 Jimmy
I'm a type A, Jimmy.
我这样的人爱打破僵局
People like me break things.
当我静下心来仔细思考时 我...
When I slow down, or when I take a minute to think about it, I...
你就是这样道歉的?
Is that your idea of an apology?
我开95码的速度过来不是道歉的
I didn't drive an hour up 95 to apologize.
我想你
I missed you.
我也想你 我想
I missed you, too, I guess.
但大老远赶来说这个...
Still, seems a long way to come just to tell me that...
还要开回华盛顿
then turn around and drive back down to DC.
我今晚不回去
I'm not driving back tonight.
最近怎么样?
So what's going on?
- 在查案吗? - 嗯
- Are you working on a case? - hmm.
是大案子
It's a good one.
你呢? 有什么新鲜事?
How about you? Anything interesting?
华盛顿那边有风传
I did hear a crazy Baltimore story...
说有一宗巴尔的摩的大案子
you know, through the rumor mill of Washington.
真的?
Really?
某个...
Some...
腐败警长肆意...
renegade Police Commander takes it on himself to...
在特区让毒品合法化?
I don't know, legalize drugs in the precinct?
市长居然还不知情?
Mayor doesn't even know about it?
你相信吗?
Can you believe that?
匪夷所思
Crazy story.
某个...
Someone...
叫Colvin的人
I think it's Colvin.
你认识他吗?
You know him?
不 算不上认识
No, I can't say that I do.
但我觉得很有趣...
Still, I think it's funny that some...
华盛顿有个大嘴巴 知道巴尔的摩警察的名字
water-cooler talker down in DC knows any Baltimore cop's name.
我只是好奇
I was just wondering.
听着 我...
Listen, I'm...
- 你要走? - 是的 我要走了
- You're leaving? - Yeah, I think so.
晚安
Good night.
该死 我已经想念这里了
Damn, man, I miss this crib already.
你在别地儿干了太久 你必须干的事
Yeah, well, you spending a lot of time at the other spot doing what you gotta do.
是啊
Yeah.
必须处理Marlo这档子事儿 让我很遗憾
Man, it's a shame we got to deal with this Marlo bullshit, man.
如果我早点处理好
I mean, if I had taken care of that earlier, man...
总会有这么个人
There's always gonna be a Marlo, man.
没有Marlo 游戏就结束了
No Marlo, no game.
但你确实可以早点处理 没错
But you could've dealt with that shit a little sooner, I mean, yeah.
但你知道 别为这事烦心了
But, you know what I'm saying? Don't let it lay on you like that.
今晚我要放松 欣赏这夜景
Tonight, I mean, I'm gonna kick back and just enjoy this view.
看看这景致 你他妈能相信吗?
I mean, look at this shit. Can you fucking believe this?
我也有个俯瞰港口的房子
I mean, I got a crib that's overlooking the Harbor.
这是同一个地方  我们曾在里头跑来跑去
This is the same place... we used to run through this motherfucker...
每个保安都狂追我们
we had every security guard in there following us.
- 他们很尽责 - 没错 没错
- As they should have. - True, true.
- 后来有一次... - 玩具店?
- And then there was that one time... - Toy store?
我告诉过你别偷那副羽毛球套装
Hell, yeah, I told your ass not to steal the badminton set.
你有网和球拍有什么用
What you gonna do with a fucking net and a racket
我们都没有球场
and we ain't got no yard.
你还说"那小子没有跳出柜台追我"
You like, "Yo, that white boy ain't gonna jump over that counter and come chase after me."
- 他确实出来了 - 然后他说...
- He sure did, though. - Then he said...
- 我说"搞什么啊?" - 他和卡尔·刘易斯一样追你
- I said, "What the fuck?" - He was on your ass like Carl Lewis.
攥紧拳头
Fists was rolled up.
你也拼命跑
Your ass was running, too, fast as you could.
捶着自己胸口疯狂地逃
Punching yourself in the chest looking all mad and shit.
那人简直拼了命
That shit was crazy, man.
也在这里 就在这里 老天
Right here, too, man, right there. Goddamn.
你相信吗? 要是我当时有现在的钱
Can you imagine, man, if I had the money that I have now, man...
我可以买半个这样的海景房产 真见鬼
I could have bought half this waterfront property. God damn it.
别去想了 兄弟
Forget about that for a while, man.
知道吗 和我一起做梦
You know, just dream with me.
我们已没有梦想 兄弟
We ain't gotta dream no more, man.
只有真正的好玩意儿
We got real shit...
看得见摸得着的房地产
real estate, we can touch.
我今晚不能喝多
I can't get too fucked up tonight, man.
明天要去工地办事
I got some shit I gotta do on the site tomorrow.
还有给我们干活的那个该死的波兰人
Plus, the fucking Polack we got working for us, man...
我要给他点教训
I gotta pull his coat.
如果他和Clay Davis有任何关系
If he had anything to do with that Clay Davis bullshit, man...
我要扣他的工钱 娘娘腔
I'm gonna have to cut his money, little faggot.
你们几点见面?
What time y'all meeting?
几点? 我想是12点 怎么了?
What time? 12:00, I think. Why?
有事要我帮忙吗?
You need me to do something for you?
没有 只想问问你几点去
No, I'm just seeing where you going to be at.
你要再放轻松点
You need to relax more, man.
时机成熟后
Well, when the time is right,
我会的
I will.
你知道 我不太把工作当回事
You know, I don't take my work too seriously.
没错
That's right.
只是生意
It's just business.
敬我们 狗日的
Us, motherfucker.
敬我们 兄弟
Us, man.
打他 Andre 去打他
Get him, Andre, go get him.
加油 Spider 打倒他
Come on, Spider, you got him. Come on.
- 没事吧? - 没事 没事
- All right? - I'm good, I'm good.
好的
All right.
- 好了 Ditty 你上 - 你为什么不还手?
- All right, Ditty, you up. - Why didn't you hit him back, man?
你来 Justin
You, Justin.
快点 孩子 我在叫你的名字
Come on, boy, I'm calling your name.
好 听好了  我们开三局 每局两分钟
All right, listen up. We gonna have three two-minute rounds.
小心腰下拳 碰手套
Watch the low blows. Touch gloves.
预备...
And...
上 Justin
Let's go, Justin.
Justin 加油 加油
Justin, come on. Come on.
很好 很好
That's good, that's good.
直拳 要快
Straight shot, come on.
把手抬起来 Justin
Get your hands up, Justin.
加油 你要挡住拳头
Come on, man. Come on. You gotta block that.
他照着左边打右边 Justin
He leading left and punching right, Justin.
- 转向他的弱点 - 他个头只到你腰部
- Move towards his weak side. - He only come up to your waist.
老天 打铃
Man, bell.
- 这两分钟真快 - 是啊 我知道
- That was a quick two minutes. - Yeah, I know.
喝点水 吐掉
Get you some water, boy, and spit it out.
- 你还好吧? - 有点晕
- You all right? - Dizzy.
所以我一直告诉要深呼吸
That's why the hell I keep telling you you got to breathe, boy.
- 怎么样? 还能打吗? - 能 我没事
- So, what? You had enough? - No, I'm good.
好的 好的
All right, all right.
上 Justin 上 Justin!
Let's go, Justin. Let's go, Justin!
加油 Justin 冲啊 Justin
Come on, Justin. Let's go, Justin.
冲啊 Justin 加油
Let's go, Justin. Come on.
刺拳 Justin 要用刺拳
Jab, Justin. Gotta jab.
嘿 有来电 准备好
Hey, we're up. Here it is.
- 是我 - 你有老板的消息吗?
- It's me, man. - You heard from the fat man?
有
Yeah.
我们没被发现吧? 一个冤大头好像怀疑了
We low, right? One mark shy of the mark.
对 是假的 Cherry说是假的
Yeah, it's light. Cherry say it's light.
告诉老板我必须这么做
Tell the man I'm doing what needs done.
好的 我会跟他说的
All right, I'll tell him.
- 哦 还有件事? - 什么?
- Oh, and that other thing? - What?
你问的两个杀手
Them two hitters you asked after.
- 他同意了 - 别在电话上讲
- He good with it. - Not on the phone.
有了
That's it.
我们等到了!
We got it!
喔
??
好样的
Good work.
我想这算中肯的
I guess this is pertinent.
没错!
Yeah!
没必要退出
Ain't no need to go back out.
你不需要证明什么
You ain't got to prove nothing.
我妈打得还要狠呢
Shoot, my momma hit me harder than that.
我还有机会 他快打疲了
I still got a chance, he getting tired.
喝口水吐掉
Drink and spit.
- 准备好了 - 你的状态很好 孩子
- Ready. - You more than ready, boy.
斗士
You game rooster.
- 上啊 Justin - 嘿 Justin
- Let's go, Justin. - Hey, Justin.
有其他入口吗?
Is there an alley entrance?
两边都有把守
Boarded up on both sides.
所以只能走大门了
So we gonna have to go through the front.
这不是你的作风吧?
That's a change for you, isn't it?
你准备好就是了 小礼服
You just be ready, Bow Tie.
懂我的意思吧?
You know what I'm talking about?
深呼吸 孩子 深呼吸
Breathe, boy. Breathe.
碰手套
Touch gloves.
- 我表现怎么样? - 你还要多加练习
- How'd I do? - You still got plenty to learn.
但说真心话?
But on the heart side?
你打得不错
You did good.
回家吧 战士 今天好好休息
Go on home, soldier. You done for the day.
我现在可算清楚了
Oh, I can see it all clearly now.
你和承包商之间是那该死的官员
Between you and them subcontractors and that motherfucking politician...
你们把我玩得团团转
y'all had me in a spin, right?
- Bell先生 我不知道... - 小矮子!
- Mr. Bell, I don't know... - Little man!
我们要解决这件事
We gonna get all this shit sorted out.
如果事情不对头
And, hey, if the shit don't come up right...
不管怎样 你来承担后果
one way or another you gonna pay for this shit.
你生气我能理解
Look, I understand you're angry
但同时你能看到我们的进展
but at the same time you can see the progress we've made in here.
- 进展 - 说实话我不知道
- Progress. - Now I honestly don't know
你和参议员Davis之间有什么过节
what passed between you and Senator Davis.
但你不爽Clayton的表现
But if you're unhappy with Clayton's performance...
你得想办法解决...
then you have to work that out...
- 见鬼 - 哦 上帝
- Shit. - Oh, God.
哦 上帝 不要
Oh, God, no.
哦 上帝 不要 不要...
Oh, God, no, no...
我没有武器
I ain't strapped.
你看 老兄
Look, man,
我没关系的了
I ain't involved.
我已经跟帮会没关系了
I ain't involved in that gangster bullshit no more.
你们想要什么?
What y'all niggers want, man?
嗯? 要钱吗?
Huh? Money?
对吗?
Is that it?
如果是钱 我活着比死了更有用
'Cause if it is, man, I can be a better friend to y'all alive.
你还是没明白吧?
You still don't get it, do you?
嗯?
Huh?
不是要你的钱 老兄
This ain't about your money, bro.
你的人供出了你
Your boy gave you up.
没错
That's right.
我们都没有对他严刑逼供
And we ain't had to torture his ass, neither.
看情形...
Well, it seem like...
我说什么也改变不了你们的主意
I can't say nothing to change y'all minds.
那就来吧 混蛋...
Well, get on with it, mother...
住宅/零售 投资机遇 来自B&B公司